--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
本电影根据真实英勇事迹改编
在我父亲去世之前 他说人老了之后 最糟糕的一件事
Before my father died, he said the worst thing about growing old
就是人们不再觉得你具有任何威胁性了
was that other men stopped seeing you as dangerous.
我一直记得这句话 具有威胁性是神圣的 是荣誉的徽章
I've always remembered that, how being dangerous was sacred, a badge of honor.
人们按照规则生活 有自己的民族精神
You live your life by a code, an ethos.
每个人都这样 它是你的海岸线 引导你回家
Every man does. It's your shoreline. It's what guides you home.
还有 相信我 无论在哪里 人们都会想回家
And, trust me, you're always trying to get home.
海豹7队
光晕跳伞训练 圣地亚哥 加利福尼亚
圣地亚哥 北纬14°35' 东经121°
菲律宾 南纬32°42’54" 东经117°9'45"
权威部门说这一范围以哥斯达黎加为中心
Authorities say the ring is centered in Costa Rica,
人们对主要出口产品...
with the primary export being...
几乎毫不知情 如果毒品之战将他们联系起来...
widely unknown if the war on drugs is connecting them...
在该区域 政府一直鼓吹利用美国...
In the region have been known to retaliate using a...
25000士兵军队...
25,000 troops...
对其控制并加以报复...
flying from the US to control that...
我们能买点冰淇淋是吗?
Can we get some ice cream?
- 不行 我们得走了  - 你总是说不行
- No, we gotta go.  - You always say no.
- 你付钱吗?  - 不 你付钱
- Well, are you gonna buy?  - No, you buy.
好吧 今天想吃什么味道的?
OK, what are we getting today?
- 百香果口味的  - 好的 那就买百香果口味的
- Passion fruit.  - OK, passion fruit.
昆士兰果的行不?
How about macadamia nut?
宣称要对在马尼拉(菲律宾首都)国际学校
Claimed responsibility for the attack
这起袭击负责
at the International School in Manila.
你父亲喜欢读书
Your father was a reader.
他喜欢邱吉尔的作品 还有福克纳的 以及关于特库姆塞的书
Churchill, of course, but also Faulkner and books about Tecumseh.
他喜欢那些将人体画成像盒子一样的艺术家
He loved artists who painted people with bodies that looked like boxes.
我对他这种爱好嗤之以鼻
I'd give him hell about that.
而他却说"你得观察得再认真一些"
He'd just say, "You gotta look harder."
马格里斯大使长久以来一直是
Ambassador Margullies had long been a strong supporter
该区域内联合反恐怖主义行动的有力支持者
of joint counterterrorism operations conducted within this region.
目前没有查出这起发生在国际学校恐怖袭击的幕后黑手
Not one group has yet claimed responsibility for the attacks on the International School.
- 这是你的咖啡 洛克  - 谢谢你 女士
- Here's your coffee, Rorke.  - Thank you, ma'am.
洛克中尉
青铜奖 美国中央司令部 4次海外部署
- 近来可好啊?  - 嘿 还跟以前一样吗?
- How's it going?  - Hey, you want the usual?
- 是的 谢谢  - 你又说迟了 戴夫
- Sounds good, thank you.  - You're late again, Dave.
戴夫
年度水手
美国太平洋司令部 5次海外派遣
美国中央司令部 2次海外派遣
我什么也没说啊
I didn't say anything.
你拿的是什么?
What do you got going on over here?
准爸爸手册
- 你开玩笑吧 伙计?  - 我们先不跟别人说
- Are you serious, man?  - We're not telling anyone yet.
你是有点紧张 对吧?
You a little nervous, though, huh?
是啊 我现在可以毫无头绪
Last time I checked, they don't come with directions.
是啊 谁说不是呢
Yeah, tell me about it.
- 嘿  - 嘿
- Hey.  - Hey.
我兄弟要当爸爸了
My man here is having a baby.
嘿 祝贺你
Hey, congratulations.
嘿 伙计们 洛克要当爸爸了
Hey, everybody, Rorke's having a baby.
祝贺你 洛克!
Congratulations, Rorke!
哇!
Whoo!
- 我刚怎么就告诉你了呢?  - 啊 别担心 伙计
- What did I just say?  - Ah, don't worry about it, man.
你会是个好爸爸的 真为你感到高兴 伙计
You're gonna be awesome. I'm so excited for you, man.
你会是个好爸爸的
You're gonna be a good dad.
嘿 明天我跟杰克要去海边玩
Hey, tomorrow Jackie and I are heading down to the beach.
带着山迪和孩子们 我多给你带个冲浪板
Bring Sandy and the kids. I'll bring an extra board for you.
- 你知道我不会冲浪  - 我知道你不会 但是
- You know I don't surf.  - I know you don't surf, but it'll be good
- 只要能跟家人在一起就行  - 好吧
- to get the families together.  - All right.
既然你已经跟整个酒吧的人都说了 明天试着控制下自己
But now that you've told everyone in the bar, try and contain yourself tomorrow.
我会尽力的
I will try.
哥斯达黎加 北纬9°55' 西经84°4'
"再仔细些观察" 你父亲会这么说
"Look harder," your father would say.
我一直都明白 他说的不仅仅只是那些盒子般抽象的画
I always knew he wasn't just talking about those boxy abstract paintings.
威胁随处可见 世界笼罩在伪装之中
There's threats everywhere, and the world is draped in camouflage.
会不会很疼啊?
不疼 就像... 轻轻一下
孩子们 你们怎么样啊?
是克里斯托
嗯?
Huh?
嘿 我这就下去 好吧?
Hey, I'll be right down, all right?
全听你的 老大
Whatever you say, Boss.
一路还好吧?
How was the ride?
我今早离开了哥伦比亚
I left Colombia this morning.
- 一天就从哥伦比亚到这里了?  - 小菜一碟
- Colombia to here in one day?  - Piece of cake.
先不管这些 有人说克里斯托
Anyway, estimates say that Christo is worth
- 身价直逼10亿  - 真的是"10亿"?
- close to a billion.  - That's with a "B"?
是的 他为自己的社区贡献了很多
Yeah, and he gives back a lot to this community over here
建了医疗诊所 学校 政治募捐
with medical clinics, schools, political donations,
等等 最重要的是
you name it, so this is the deal:
在这里 他们都对他十分忠诚
They are extremely loyal to him over here.
美国缉毒局什么时候把他移交给我们?
When did the DEA hand him over to us?
等他们拦截了他满载了苏联武器的波音707客机
When they intercepted a 707 of his filled with Soviet weapons.
听着 中情局的人说国家安全局的人
Listen, Langley says that the boys over at NSA,
对情报进行了拦截 发现克里斯托
they found some interesting intercepts connecting Christo
与东南亚之外的圣战主义者组织联系
to a jihadist network out of Southeast Asia.
显然 克里斯托和其中一人操纵着那个组织
Apparently, Christo and one of the guys running the network,
他们是儿时的朋友
they're childhood friends.
你父亲的祖父在第二次世界大战中
Your father's grandfather gave up his life
驾驶着B-24轰炸机牺牲了
flying a B-24 in World War II.
他坚持驾驶飞机很久 使得每个人都有足够的时间跳下去
He kept the Liberator aloft just long enough for everyone to jump,
之后随着飞机一起坠毁了
and then he went down with the plane.
你身体里也流淌着他英勇的血液
That's the blood that courses in your veins.
- 爸爸 我能跟你一起去吗?  - 你想跟我一起去吗?
- Daddy, can I come with you?  - You want to come with me?
你感觉到海水多凉了吗? 我跟你说
Did you feel how cold it is out there? I'll tell you what,
去跟你妈妈玩吧 帮她带着弟弟妹妹
go hang out with Mommy for a little while, help out with the baby.
等我回来 如果你还想去 那我就带你去玩
When I come back in, if you still want to go out, I'll take you out with me.
- 你保证?  - 我保证 快去吧 快去
- Promise?  - I promise. Hurry up, go.
- 怎么样 伙计?  - 怎么了 兄弟?
- What's going on, sir?  - What's up, brother?
- 没什么 兄弟  - 我知道你们纽约人都这样
- Nothing much, man.  - Now, I know you got the New York heritage,
但这跟待在斯塔顿岛可不一样
but this isn't exactly like sitting back in Staten Island.
要想学会冲浪 你可要非常地努力
You got to actually work hard to get through the surf.
- 是啊 我知道  - 你可是有12多年的从军经验
- Yeah, I know.  - Twelve-plus years on the Teams,
真的不知道怎么玩?
and you don't know how to do this?
嘿 等到你有5个孩子了 伙计
Hey, wait till you have five kids, man.
你就知道你有没有时间冲浪了
You'll see how much time you got to play in the surf.
准备好下海了吗?
You ready to get in the drink or what?
好吧 兄弟 你带路
All right, man, lead the way.
- 好的 别给我们丢脸  - 没问题
- All right, don't embarrass us.  - All right.
你爸爸是我的头儿 我是他的副手
Your father was my Boss, and I was his Chief.
我们对彼此的了解 将我们以指挥者的身份紧密联系在了一起
What we knew about each other strengthened our bond as operators.
我们亲如兄弟
There was a brotherhood between us,
我们比亲人更依赖对方
and we depended on each other more than a family.
特库姆塞曾说过 "一根筷子易折断
Tecumseh said, "Although a single twig will break,
一捆筷子力量坚"
a bundle of twigs is strong."
你走过了!
是二楼的铸铁大门
好的 好的 谢谢
OK, OK, gracias.
哇哦 真是难以置信
Wow, this is unbelievable.
真不敢相信你竟然在这里点中餐
I still can't believe you ordered Chinese in this place.
真的很好吃
It's really good.
双字得分 18分
Double word score, 18 points.
- "哑巴"?  - 看一下 别难过 宝贝
- "Dumb"?  - Read it and weep, sugar.
放心 我不会的
I'll try not to.
看这个 还有这个 我得了38分
Look at this, look at this. Thirty-eight points for me.
"择避" 根本就不是个词
"Adumbrating," that's not even a word.
好吧 首先 发音是"遮蔽"
OK, first of all, it's pronounced "adumbrating,"
意思是伪装 预兆
and it means pretending, foreshadowing.
嗯...
Hm...
看来今天的晚饭你得请了 宝贝
guess who's buying dinner tonight, sugar.
好吧
Fine.
大部分情况下 军官都有战略伙伴
In most cases, officers get tactical partners.
中情局却分配了个拼字作弊的搭档给我
Langley sets me up with some sort of SCRABBLE hustler.
拼字大师 好吧? 记住了
SCRABBLE Yoda, OK? Get it right.
- 多少钱?  - 免费的
- How much do I owe you?  - Nada.
靠
Shit.
我们野战排要去执行海外派遣任务
Our platoon was headed downrange.
威米
"V"字铜星奖章
美国中央司令部 2次海外部署
美国太平洋地区司令部 1次海外部署
紫心勋章
军队嘉奖奖章
我们有威米 他是狙击手
We had Weimy, our sniper.
他在莫哈韦沙漠中心长大
He grew up in the middle of the Mojave Desert.
孩提时 对他来说最令人兴奋的事就是
Most excitement he found as a kid was bowling frozen turkeys
在杂货店里找到用碗装的冻火鸡
down the aisle at the grocery store.
瑞 使我们的通讯使者 负责无线电
Ray, our comms guy, our radioman,
瑞
银星奖章
"V"字铜星奖章
美国中央司令部 2次海外部署
美国太平洋军区 1次海外部署
在洛杉矶东部的黑社会长大
he grew up in East LA gangland.
曾因在交火中救出受伤战友获得银星奖章
He had a Silver Star for pulling a wounded teammate out of the fray.
索尼
7年排爆操作员经验
美国南方司令部 2次海外部署
美国中央司令部 1次海外部署
美国太平洋军区 1次海外部署
索尼 身材非常魁梧
Sonny, he was made of granite.
他都不想做俯卧撑
This guy didn't even do push-ups
因为他怕胸部太大
'cause he was afraid his chest was gonna get too big.
阿杰
美国中央司令部 1次海外部署
美国太平洋军区 1次海外部署
阿杰快40岁才加入到这个团队中
Ajay joined the Teams late in his 30s.
早期他是一名泰拳选手
He'd been a Muay Thai fighter early in life.
在此之前 他生活在贫穷落后的特立尼达拉岛
Before that, he grew up dirt-poor in Trinidad.
麦克
美国太平洋军区 5次海外部署
美国中央司令部 1次海外部署
麦克在队里待了20年了
Mikey had 20 years in the Teams.
但他非常谦逊 永远那么多低调
But as humble as he was, you'd never even know it.
他的头盔里有他妻子的照片 口袋里有他妻子的头发
He kept a picture of his wife in his helmet and a lock of her hair in his pocket.
安静的就像微风一般
Quiet as the breeze.
米勒
美国中央司令部 4次海外部署
美国太平洋军区 2次海外部署
还有副排长
And finally, Senior Chief.
关于他 我真的不想说什么...
I couldn't really tell you much about him...
我宁愿拿着小刀参加枪战
other than I'd rather take a knife into a gunfight
也不愿意受他审问
than have to be interrogated by him.
在家的最后一晚
That last night at home,
我们都在想着该怎么做个好父亲
you think about how you could have been a better dad,
好丈夫
a better husband.
记得睡觉前个孩子讲故事 记住婚礼周年纪念日
That bedtime story you should have read or that anniversary you forgot.
我们不指望家人能理解我们的工作
You don't expect your family to understand what you're doing,
但至少希望他们能够接受
you just hope they'll accept it.
再回到家时 希望可以继续跟家人和谐相处
When you get home, you hope you can pick up right where you left off.
还好吧?
What up?
- 把你的野孩子们哄睡着了啊?  - 是啊 没错
- You putting the wild bunch down?  - Yeah, yeah.
嘿 副排长 能让们单独处一会儿吗 伙计?
Hey, Senior, you mind giving us a couple minutes, man?
- 好的 那我先走了 杰夫  - 谢谢
- Nah, you got 'em, Jefe.  - Thanks.
嘿 兄弟们 你们都知道我只有在诊断检查
Hey, fellas, you know I only got so many speeches
和部署的时候 才说这么多话 但这次 呃...
in a given work-up or deployment, but, uh...
就像副排长和我在这个排成立之初说的那样:
it's like Chief and I said right at the beginning of this platoon:
一旦我们决定出发 上飞机执行海外派遣任务
Once we step off on campaign, once this bird's ready and we're downrange,
家里的一切都不要再牵挂了
everything back home needs to be in balance.
如果因为这些出了事
We're not gonna be worth a damn to each other or ourselves
不管对大家还是对个人来说都太不值了
if we get over there and something's out of whack.
我是说 如果家里遇到了危机
I mean, if things aren't right with the family,
出现了资金问题或者其它什么的
things aren't right with the finances or something's off,
都会让我们分心的 所以在我们出发之前 一定要先说清楚
it's gonna put us all out of balance, so we need to have that tight before we launch.
如果有人有问题 就提出来
If somebody's got an issue, bring it up.
副队长可以帮助解决 我也能 我们大家互相帮助
Chief can take care of it, I can take care of it. Everybody's got each other's back.
所以要知道轻重缓急 等我们出发了
Let's make sure we lock that down so when we're ready to roll,
目标就只能是完成任务
all our focus is on the mission.
敬我们自己 以及和我们一样
For all those who have been downrange,
所有去海外执行任务的军人
to us and those like us, damn few.
- 干杯  - 干了
- Cheers.  - Cheers.
我还是喜欢詹姆斯这个名字
I still like the name James.
要是男孩 我会考虑的
I'll think about it, if it's a boy.
过来抱抱
Come here.
- 为你骄傲  - 谢谢你 宝贝
- I'm proud of you.  - Thanks, baby.
嘿 小家伙 让你妈妈里卡罗姑妈远点
Hey, little one, you make sure you keep Mama away from Aunt Carol.
我很不喜欢她不停地抽烟
I don't like that chain-smoking at all.
我知道了 中尉
I got it, Lieutenant.
- 好的  - 会没事的
- OK.  - It's gonna be OK.
- 好吧  - 会没事的
- All right.  - It's gonna be fine.
头发要一直留着不许剪 知道吗?
Try to keep this as long as you can for a while, yeah?
还有其它的吗 长官?
Anything else, Commander?
有 在我们第一个孩子出生时 我想要你待在身边
Yeah. I'd like to be able to look into your eyes when our first child is born.
你知道我会尽力的
You know I'll do my best.
我爱你 宝贝
I Iove you, baby.
爱你
Love you.
战争是由国家决定的
War is a country of will.
没有任何同情可言
There's no room for sympathy.
如果你放不下所有的一切 你就已经输了
If you're not willing to give up everything, you've already lost.
我们抓到她了 但她杀了吉尔伯特
就是她 老大
我怎么了? 我干什么了!
我是墨西哥的一名医生
你们想要干什么?
跟我说说 你们美国人到底有什么权利
Tell me, what is it about you Americans that makes
让你来捣乱我的计划?
you feel entitled to fuck with the way I make my living?
乌克兰 北纬50°27' 东经30°30'
我叫丽莎・翁 是一名墨西哥医生
你想从我这里知道什么?
我已经跟这个人说了 我什么都不知道
我知道你是谁 莫拉莱斯小姐 我也知道你为谁工作
I know who you are, Miss Morales, and I know who you work for.
不如就爽快点
So why don't you save us both some time
告诉我你所知道的一切吧?
and tell me exactly what you think you know?
我专杀生你这种人渣的老妈
听到了吗 人渣?
感觉如何 莫拉莱斯小姐?
How did that feel, Miss Morales?
好好享受下矿泉浴吧
Have a great day at the spa.
关掉扬声器
留活口 等她说了再给我打电话
明白了 头儿
Si, Jefe.
说不说?
女巫岩营地 哥斯达黎加
- 嘿 伙计们 都还好吧?  - 嘿
- Hey, fellas, what's up?  - Hey.
比两只耗子卷到羊毛袜子里面还热 对吧?
It's hotter than two rats screwing in a wool sock out there, yeah?
非洲是很热... 连泰山都受不了的
Africa-hot... Tarzan couldn't take this heat.
好了 说正事 蛙人们注意听了(蛙人:水下侦查员)
Anyway, here's the deal. Time to get your frogman on.
关灯 3天前
Lights. Three days ago,
两位中情局的特工 沃特・罗斯和丽莎・莫拉莱斯小姐
two CIA agents, a Walter Ross and a Miss Lisa Morales,
在哥斯达黎加的酒店内遭遇埋伏
were ambushed inside their hotel room here in Costa Rica
埋伏人员是一群武装严密的人渣
by a unknown amount of heavily armed assholes.
不幸的是 罗斯先生被杀害 莫拉莱斯小姐被绑架
Unfortunately, Mr. Ross was murdered, and Miss Morales has been abducted.
我们认为 这起事件与
We believe that this has been the work
一个名叫米哈伊尔・特洛伊卡维奇的人 也就是克里斯托有关
of a guy named Mikhail Troykavitch, aka Christo.
中尉将会告知你们关于他的细节
LT's going to give you the skinny on him.
谢谢你长官 米哈伊尔・特洛伊卡维奇 又名克里斯托
Thanks, Senior. Mikhail Troykavitch, aka Christo.
有证据显示他从事可卡因和武器交易
This guy is believed to have been working cocaine-for-weapons deals
交易对象有俄罗斯黑手党 哥伦比亚革命武装部队游击队和墨西哥贩毒集团
between the Russian mafia, the FARC guerrillas, and the Mexican drug cartels
最早始于20世纪90年代末
ever since the late 1990s.
在被抓之前 莫拉莱斯一直在查
Now, before she was captured, Morales was working a possible link
我们的目标克里斯托和这个名叫阿布・沙宝之间的关系
between our boy Christo and this guy Abu Shabal.
是真主阿拉 世界之主
Glory to Allah, Lord of the worlds,
创造了我们穆斯林人
who has created us as Muslims
并引导我们讨伐异教徒
and delivered us with the jihad on his direct path.
在审判末日到来之前 只要遵循她的旨意 就会平安无事
Peace be upon those who follow his direct path till the Day of Judgment.
我给你们美国人解释一下吧
Let me explain this to you Americans.
我们不是分离主义分子
We are not separatists.
在所有人看来 我们车臣人都是恐怖分子
We Chechens are not a legal part of anyone,
但你们美国人却随意对我们
but you Americans are willingly or unwillingly assisting
进行种族灭绝 要我们遵守你们的某些规则
in the genocide of our people by demanding that we obey certain rules,
好让你们能够继续占领所有穆斯林国家
and by your continued occupation of all Muslim countries.
愿真主阿拉保佑 他是那么的高尚与伟大
With the grace of Allah, glorious and exalted is he,
如果不能确保我们的安全 美国将永远处于恐怖主义笼罩之中
America will never be safe until safety becomes a reality for us.
阿拉万岁
Allahu Akbar.
阿布・沙宝是车臣恐怖分子
Abu Shabal is a Chechen terrorist
曾参与了别斯兰人质事件
who's associated with the Beslan School Massacre.
他一直周转于印度尼西亚和菲律宾的集训营
He's been jumping between training camps in Indonesia and the Philippines.
虽然现在我们队克里斯托和阿布・沙宝之间的联系不是很清楚
Now, the connection between Christo and Abu Shabal is still a little bit fuzzy,
但如果莫拉莱斯一直在调查这些
but if this was the lead that Morales was working on,
这也就是她被绑架的原因 有补充的吗 长官?
it could be why she was abducted. Senior?
好了 此次是对进行莫拉莱斯小姐的救援行动
All right, this is a personnel recovery of Miss Morales.
好了 有问题吗?
All right, who's got questions?
长官 有营地内部人员数目
Senior Chief, you got any updated source intel
包括巡逻队的最新资料吗?
on numbers inside the camp, and what about roving patrols?
大概有8到10个人 兄弟 但对于巡逻队 我们毫不知情
Maybe eight to ten, bro, but we don't know anything about roving patrols.
所以你要当成他们就在外面巡逻
You're just gonna have to assume that they're out there
整装待发 他们也是以此为生的
walking around, squared away. They do this for a living, too.
长官 目标人员所持有的武器如何?
Senior, what kind of weapons-on-target are we looking at?
他们持有重武器 这些家伙都是毒枭
Heavy weapons. These guys are narco-traffickers,
任何苏制德什卡重武器 他们都可能有
so they can have anything from Soviet-bloc DShks.
可能持有M2HP以及.5口径的突击步枪 我们没有确切情报
They could have M2HP, .50-cals out there, we don't know.
那里很可能会有军火库 所以我建议你们带上火箭筒
So if there is a weapons' emplacement up there, I suggest you guys bring rockets.
注意一点 火箭会烧着附近的植物 因此你们必须确保一次就命中目标
Of course, rockets and foliage don't match, so make sure you got a clear shot.
- 好的 还有什么问题?  - 人质还有行动能力吗?
- All right, what else?  - Any idea whether she's ambulatory or not?
现场血迹斑斑
There was a ton of blood on the scene,
我们的人已经确认过 那些主要是罗斯先生的血迹
and a lot of it was Mr. Ross', we confirmed that.
还有一部分可能是莫拉莱斯女士的 这些人是禽兽
Miss Morales may have bled there, too, but these guys are savages,
暂且假定人质已没有行动能力
so you're gonna have to assume that she is non-ambulatory,
所以你们得带上抬她出来的家伙
so you're gonna have to bring stuff to carry her out.
跳伞倒计时两分钟
Two minutes to drop.
嘿 中尉
Hey, LT.
你得告诉我们那个家伙是谁 咱们回来之后就帮你去教训他
You got to let us know who that guy is, so when we get back, we can kick his ass.
那个家伙?
What guy?
把你发型整得跟狗啃似的那个
The guy that gave you that fucked-up haircut.
- 滚  - 你真可恶 索尼
- Fuck.  - Damn, Sonny,
什么时候轮到你来评论了啊 你的也不怎么样 看起来跟多明尼亚人似的
you should be the last guy to talk. You look like the Dominican Mr. Clean.
那只能说明我的头跟你的金牙一样亮晶晶的 对吧?
That means my head shines like your gold teeth, huh?
别这样说
Don't be like that,
- 你太损了  - 打开滑行台!
- that's harsh.  - Ramp!
戴上面罩
Mask up.
伙计 跟你说吧 当一个准爸爸是唯一值得欣慰的事
Man, I tell you what. The only thing better than this right here is being a dad,
除了换尿布那种事 但...
except for that whole changing diaper thing, but...
山迪会帮我搞定的 所以...
Sandy does that for me anyway, so...
我还是挺激动的
I'm actually looking forward to it.
黑胡子 10秒后起跳
Blackbeard, green light in ten.
5秒
Five.
黑胡子总部 黑胡子总部 我们是黑胡子行动人员
Blackbeard Main, Blackbeard Main, this is Blackbeard Actual.
无线电测试 完毕
Radio check. Over.
黑胡子总部 黑胡子总部 我们是黑胡子行动人员 完毕
Blackbeard Main, Blackbeard Main, this is Blackbeard Actual. Over.
收到 行动人员 这里是总部
Roger, Actual. This is Main.
- 听得非常清楚  - 收到 总部
- We have you Lima Charlie.  - Roger, Main.
所有人员已安全降落 向雷鸟行进
All boots are on the ground. I pass T-bird.
有敌人向我方靠近吗?
Any traffic for my station at this time?
行动人员 幻想号在第二目标位置发现了
Actual, imagery picked up an increase in traffic
敌人的快速应变小组
at secondary location, known to be enemy QRF,
距离原始目标有8千米
eight clicks from primary target.
特种部队运输船会在0600位置为你们清道
The SWCC boats will insert at 0600 for your extract.
- 明白吗?  - 收到 总部
- How copy?  - Roger, Main.
- 准备好了吗?  - 是的 长官
- You ready?  - Roger that, sir.
我们距离355号目标大约有4.7千米远
We got about 4.7 clicks at three-five-five.
行动
Take it out.
战鞭 降落倒计时1分钟
Whiplash, one minute out.
三十秒
Thirty seconds.
10秒
Ten by ten.
战鞭 行动
Whiplash, go.
所有人员已登上甲板
All boots on deck.
绳索已解除
Line secure.
战鞭 一号船与二号船已出发
Whiplash, Bucket One and Two are out.
战鞭 我们是黑胡子分队 无线电测试 结束
Whiplash, this is Blackbeard. Radio check. Over.
黑胡子 我们是战鞭分队 信号清晰
Blackbeard, it's Whiplash. Have you loud and clear.
随时准备接应
Standing by on the set.
收到 黑胡子 你们到达指定位置还要多长时间?
Roger, Whiplash. What is your ETA to my pos?
大约20海里的航程
ETA 20 mikes.
注意 乌鸦号已升空 正向你们的位置推进
Be advised, Raven is in flight and pushing to your location.
不!
No!
不要!
嘿 长官 我们得行动了
Hey, sir, we gotta go.
好吧 行动
Roger. Take it out.
我们人手不够 我想让你们一起行动
I feel like we're pretty thin. I'd like to take you guys with us.
副排长 冲锋艇小队正在赶来 乌鸦号也在靠近
Chief, I got a SBT coming up on-step. I got a Raven pushing my pos.
威米和我在这里掩护
Weimy and I are in good overwatch position,
我还得向黑胡子总部报告
and I got to keep reporting back to Blackbeard Main.
- 原地待命  - 明白
- We're staying here.  - Roger that.
- 瞄准点  - 明白
- Keep it tight.  - Got it.
战鞭队 我们是黑胡子分队 分队准备提前行动
Whiplash, this is Blackbeard. Assault force is moving to the target early.
请立即进行火力支援
Request immediate fire support.
黑胡子分队 我们是战鞭分队 收到
Blackbeard, it's Whiplash. Good copy.
请求火力支援 距离你们的位置还有15海里
Requesting fire support. Pushing to your location in 15 mikes.
战鞭 我们是黑胡子 乌鸦号部署完毕
Whiplash, this is Blackbeard. I have positive control of the Raven.
队长 到位了吗?
Chief, are you set?
队长 队长 原地待命
Chief, Chief, hold it.
一点钟 塔底位置
One o'clock, base of the tower.
收到
Got him.
门前障碍已扫除
You're clear to the door.
后门有两个目标
I've got two squirters coming out the back door.
突破!
Going in!
- 安全!  - 一切安全!
- Clear!  - All clear!
威米 11点钟方向 卡车驾驶员位置
Weimy, eleven o'clock. Driver's side, truck.
明白
Got him.
该死
Fuck.
- 来啊  - 冲! 冲!
- Come on.  - Go in! Go in!
- 安全!  - 一切安全
- Clear!  - All clear!
- 人质安全  - 队长 我去看看麦克
- Target's secure.  - Chief, I'm going to get Mikey.
中尉 我是队长 人质已安全
LT, this is Chief. Target is secure.
正在确认人质身份
Stand by for confirmation of the package.
注意 麦克中弹 麦克中弹 等待回复
Be advised Mikey is down. Mikey is down. Status to follow.
收到 可以进行
Roger. You have the package.
队长 我捡到一部手机了
Chief, I got his cell phone.
中尉? 快看?
LT? LT?
队长 北部有两辆敌军车辆正向你们靠近
Chief, looks like you have two aggressor vehicles approaching from the north,
距离你们还有一英里 你们可乘西门卡车离开
about one mike out. You can take the truck outside the west door.
我们在指定位置碰头
Meet us at extract.
莫拉莱斯女士 我们带你回家
Miss Morales, I'm bringing you home.
在这之前 我得问你几个问题
I just need to ask you a few questions.
你母亲的娘家姓是什么?
What's your mother's maiden name?
罗萨莱斯
Rosales.
你的出生地是哪儿?
What street you were born on?
温泉街
Hot Springs.
好的 坚持一下
All right. Just hang on.
战鞭 北部有敌军的快速反应部队向我们逼近
Whiplash, we have enemy QRF approaching from the north.
收到 敌方的快速反应部队正向你们逼近
Roger. You have enemy QRF coming in from the north.
队长 你们现在就得撤出了
Chief, you need to start your exfil now.
- 我们在第二撤离点碰头  - 收到
- We'll meet you at secondary extract.  - Roger that.
嘿 兄弟们 行动起来!
Hey, boys, we gotta roll!
该死 长官 卡车来了
Shit. Sir, it's those trucks,
- 还有1000码  - 看到了
- About 1,000 yards.  - Yep.
女士 我现在就带你走
Ma'am, I'm taking you out right now.
嘿 队长 子弹从他眼睛射入 从耳后射出
Hey, Chief, he took a round to the eye with the exit wound behind the ear.
他还活着 我们得快点车里!
He's alive, but we gotta get moving now!
威米 快出来
Weimy, coming out.
我们在集合地点碰头
We'll meet you at the rally point.
出发! 出发! 开车!
Let's go! Let's go! Move it!
- 小心! 左前方有敌军!  - 右转! 向右转!
- Heads up! Fast movement on the left!  - Right turn! Right turn!
嘿 兄弟 我们恐怕不能到达第二撤离点了
Hey, man, we're not going to make it to secondary extract.
我得认一下路
I got to find us a route. Stay on this road.
- 左 左 左  - 左转! 向左转!
- Left, left, left. - Left turn! Left turn!
麦克 醒醒 伙计
Mikey, come on, buddy.
嘿 队长!
Hey, Chief!
我们到不了第二撤离点
We're not gonna make secondary extract!
- 想办法解决这个问题 伙计!  - 等一下!
- You're gonna have to figure it out, man!  - Hold on!
拜托 醒醒 别睡过去
Come on. Stay with me. Stay with me.
别睡过去
Stay with us.
坚持 麦克 醒醒 醒醒 坚持下去 伙计
Come on, Mike. Wake up. Wake up. Come on, man.
- 交火!  - 战斗 继续战斗
- Contact!  - Pick it up, pick it up.
嗨 长官 我们能到补给点!
Yo, Chief! We can make it to rally point!
- 就这样! 通知中尉!  - 坚持啊 伙计
- Sounds good! Pass it to LT!  - Come on, man.
中尉 中尉 我们是行动队 我们不能到达第二撤离点了
LT, LT, this is assault team. We just lost the secondary extract.
重复 我们到不了第二撤离点了
I say again, we just lost secondary extract.
我们正向补给点前进 听到请回复 完毕?
Moving to rally point. How copy, over?
- 我们离那还有1千米  - 麦克 醒醒
- We're about a click out.  - Mikey, wake up.
还有一千米!
One click out!
快点 麦克 醒醒 坚持住 伙计
Let's go, Mike. Wake up. Come on, buddy.
坚持下去 麦克! 醒醒!
Come on, Mikey! Wake up!
- 准备好了吗?  - 后方安全
- Good?  - Backstage clear.
发射!
Rocket out!
他没呼吸了!
He's not breathing!
- 呼吸啊 麦克!  - 我们上车了! 出发!
- Breathe, Mikey!  - We're up! We're up!
队长 把你的M4给我!
Chief, let me get your M-4!
长官 那些船有什么标识?
Sir, what's the status on those boats?
我跟战鞭分队失去联系了
I lost Whiplash on the run.
已经告诉他们你提前打击了目标 他们现在正猛烈反扑
Told 'em you hit the target early. They're coming in hot.
- 收到  - 该死! 喝啊 伙计
- Roger that.  - Fuck! Take this, man.
呼吸 坚持啊 米奇
Breathe, Mikey. Come on, Mikey.
- 他没脉搏了  - 后方交火!
- I got no pulse.  - Contact rear!
后方交火!
Contact rear!
该死!
Holy shit!
把好方向盘...
Taking rounds in...
开枪 战斗
Pick it up. Pick it up.
阿杰! 快速反应部队快要追上来了!
Ajay! QRF coming up the rear!
战鞭! 战鞭! 第二撤离点已暴露
Whiplash! Whiplash! Secondary extract is burnt.
直接去第三撤离点
Moving to tertiary extract.
这儿共有8人 七名士兵 一名人质
I have eight packs, seven Sierras, one package.
人质身上多处负伤
Package with multiple wounds.
一名士兵头部中枪
The Sierra has gunshot wound to the head.
形势很危急
This will be a hot extract.
出了什么事?!
What the fuck?!
- 哦 该死!  - 麦克 躺好!
- Oh, shit!  - Mikey, stay down!
- 让他趴下 伙计!  - 我这他妈的是在哪儿?!
- Keep him down, man!  - Where the fuck am I?!
- 冷静点 兄弟  - 麦克醒了 哥们 麦克醒了
- Calm down, brother.  - Mikey's up, man. Mikey's up.
躺好 兄弟 冷静点 没事儿的 我们就要到安全的地方了
Stay down, brother. Calm. Be easy. We're almost out of here.
我们就要到安全的地方了
We're almost out of here.
麦克!
Mikey!
- 坚持 伙计  - 我们在哪儿?
- Hang on, buddy.  - Where are we?
- 我们正赶往撤离点  - 发生什么了?
- We're on our way to extract.  - What happened?
你会没事的 你头部中了一枪 伙计
You're good to go. You took one to the face, man.
你的命真他妈硬
You're a hard motherfucker.
- 人质救出来了吗?  - 是的
- Did we get her?  - Yes.
- 哦 天呐  - 我们正赶往撤离点呢
- Oh, my God.  - We're on our way to extract.
阿杰 有水 有水
Ajay, splash it. Splash it.
前方遇水! 前方遇水!
Water! Water! Water!
来啦! 来啦!
Going in! Going in!
我抓稳她了! 抓稳了!
I got her! I got her!
车在下沉
It's fucking going under.
出去! 快出去!
Out! Get the fuck out!
我们并非一无所获
It wasn't for nothing.
乌克兰 北纬50°27' 东经30°30’
有什么事?
是门德尔松的作品吗?
不 是 勃拉姆斯的
克里姆是哪位?
你一定是沙宝?
我跟克里斯托在电话中谈过
我有你想要的东西
很轻吧?
你可以穿在晚礼服里面
里面装满了瓷制弹珠
有五百多个
弹珠被编进衬衫里
再填装一种新型的爆炸性凝胶
杀伤力巨大
看这个
我知道 这个看起来杀伤力不怎么大
但这是专为公共场合设计的
相信我 这世上没有任何一种单人操纵的武器
能在杀伤力上跟它相媲美
瞧
没有比这个更安全的了
你穿着这件衣服进出白宫都不会被发现
你能示范一下吗?
你有时间开车去西伯利亚吗?
这个爆炸的话... 没人能幸免
想象一下 随着剧烈的爆炸...
500发子弹朝着四面八方射出
要是穿一件去像那样的体育馆
一个赌场 或是购物中心
你绝对会造成媒体恐慌...
你就达成目的了... 经济会完全崩溃
孩子 瞧你
风采依旧啊
要帮您拿大衣吗?
不用了 谢谢
要知道 我总会时不时的
You know, from time to time,
去看看我以前的那些老朋友
I get to see my old friends from my old life.
但他们总是让我失望
And it's always, always disappointing.
一些成为了混蛋 其他的让人厌烦
Some become assholes, other boring,
真不敢相信 以前我竟然会花大把精力去哄骗她们上床
and I can't believe I tried to get them in bed all those years ago.
嘿
Hey.
但你从没让我失望过 尤里
It is nice not to be disappointed, Yuri.
- 我的名字不叫尤里  - 我知道
- That's not my name.  - I know.
默罕默德・阿布・沙宝 沙宝家族的后裔
Mohammed Abu Shabal, the son of Shabal.
得了 你的父亲名字可是尤维基尼
Come on. Your father's name is Yevgeny.
时代变了
Things change.
是啊 时代变了
Yeah, things have changed.
这就是为什么 这是咱俩最后一次见面的原因了
That's why this is the last time we might have to see each other for quite some time.
我现在真想找个地方躲会儿
For I might have to find a hole to hide in.
我不太明白
I don't understand.
我被中情局监控了 我不想冒险
I'm being watched by the CIA, and I'm not taking any chances.
只要一有机会 我就会带我的家人去南部
As soon as the opportunity presents itself, I'm taking my family south.
我没有能力也没精力去跟美国人斗了
I neither have the energy or the will to fight the Americans.
那我们的交易怎么办 米哈伊尔?
What about our deal, Mikhail?
我的人已经训练了将近一年了
My men have been training for almost a year now.
- 我倾家荡产去...  - 交易还成立 尤里
- I have devoted much of my resources...  - The deal stands, Yuri.
我提前退休并不意味着
Just because I've taken early retirement does not mean
咱们之间的交易就此中断
I'm not holding up my end of the bargain.
还有很多事需要做
There is so much to be done.
没我 你们也一样能成
And it will be, just without me.
你还可以跟我信任的伙伴合作
You'll have to use my trusted associates.
我也不这样想
That's not so good for me.
- 嘿...  - 嘿! 闭嘴!
- Hey...  - Hey! Shut up!
闭上你的臭嘴!
Shut up!
别在这扯淡了!
Stop your fucking bullshit!
那怎么行 行不通的 你不能半路撂挑子
It's not good. Doesn't work. You can't change it like that.
- 什么都没变  - 你还有脸说什么都没变
- Nothing changes. Nothing.  - You just told me everything's changed.
那... 你这算怎么回事? 你说啊?
What... what is that? What is that?
你知道我费了多大劲才走到今天这地步?!
Do you know what I do to get here?!
你知道我牺牲了多少手下吗?!
Do you know the men who I've had to sacrifice to get here?!
你知道吗?!
Do you have any idea?!
你知道个屁! 你就知道自己享受纸醉金迷的生活!
No, you shit! You live up here in this ivory tower!
你不... 对别人你一点都不在乎!
You have no... you don't care!
美国中央海岸 北纬12°9’ 西经86°16’
嘿 队长 麦克怎么样了?
Hey, Chief, what's the status on Mikey?
他的眼睛是保不住了 但他... 能活下去
He's definitely gonna lose the eye, but he's... he's hanging tough.
嘿 我必须得说
Hey, I'm gonna get reed this.
干得好 教训了那些家伙 把莫拉莱斯救了回来
Greatjob smoke-checking those assholes and getting Morales back.
虽然麦克负伤了 但我还是得说 干得真不错
It's a bum deal for Mikey, but I gotta tell you what, that was solid work.
队长 你得马上把消息传达给你的弟兄
So, Chief, you make sure you get that down to the boys right away.
- 听清了吗?  - 明白
- You hear me?  - Check.
好了 再说说莫拉莱斯 她可真是坚强
All right. Now, Morales, Morales was one tough chick,
但她本该早点汇报这些情况的
but she should've gotten the stuff up the chain a lot faster
这件事比我们预想的要严重得多
because this thing is way bigger than we thought it was.
怎么回事? 我以为这只是一次美国公民的营救任务
How is that? I thought this was a cut-and-dry AMCIT recovery.
在你们捡到那部手机之前的确如此
Yeah, it was until we got into that phone that you guys picked up in that shithole.
那让我意识到事情根本没那么简单
It turned me on to something that just does not look right at all.
- 那到底哪里不对呢?  - 克里斯托和沙宝的关系比我们想像的
- And what's not right about it?  - Christo and Shabal are a lot closer
要密切得多 沙宝只是个棋子而已 伙计
than I thought they were, and Shabal is a wild card, man.
他虽是个老派基地分子 根本不在乎钱和毒品
He is an old-school jihadi that couldn't give a rat's ass about money or drugs.
是的 那他童年的朋友克里斯托是毒贩子吗?
Yeah, and his childhood friend, Christo, the dope dealer?
他不是个毒枭 而是走私犯
He is not a dealer, man. He's a smuggler.
- 你在开玩笑吧  - 我也希望是这样
- You have got to be kidding me.  - That is exactly what I'm thinking.
沙宝想袭击美国人
Shabal wants to kill Americans.
克里斯托知道怎么把他弄进美国
Christo knows how to get fuckers inside America.
在中国这可是严重的问题 伙计们
This could be big trouble in little China, fellas.
他们想在美国本土袭击我们
They're gonna hit us at home.
我刚跟上司和特别行动小组谈过了
I just got done talking to the boss and the Spec Ops Task Force,
这就是我们的计划
and this is what's gonna go down.
我要瑞和阿杰待命 两小时后执行一项特种侦察任务
I need Ajay and Ray standing by to launch for an SR in two hours.
一路飞到非洲 他俩又可以积攒很多飞行里程数了
They're gonna get some frequent flyer miles on the way to Africa.
为什么去非洲?
Why Africa?
根据你找到的手机 我们在那地方发现了一个飞机场
We pinned an airfield there with that phone that you got,
我认为沙宝会在那里
and I think that Shabal is gonna be there
完成武器交易然后西进
doing a weapons transfer on his way west.
你说的西进 是什么意思 去墨西哥的西面?
When you say "west," what are we talking about, Mexico west?
算是吧 墨西哥西面 那是最坏的情况了
Yeah, Mexico west. That's worst-case scenario.
你们和排里剩下的人在这里待命
You two and the rest of the platoon are gonna stay here on standby.
万一美国国土附近出了什么岔子
You'll be the primary assault force
你们就是主要的突击力量了
in case something goes down anywhere near America.
- 明白  - 明白
- Check.  - Check.
如果有什么情况要向你汇报的话 你还会在这里吗?
You gonna be around for any questions as they come up?
才不呢 克里斯托...这家伙好好的戏弄了咱们一番 现在又消失了
No, man. Christo... he pulled a Roman Polanski on my ass and disappeared.
所以我要联系第四海豹突击队
So I'm gonna link up with SEAL Team Four,
在南太平洋上把他打得满地找牙
and we're gonna go hunt his ass down in the South Pacific.
那我就去享受鸡尾酒和棕榈树啦
So it's straight up Mai Tais and palm trees for me, baby.
没问题 伙计 手到擒来啊
Yeah, brother. Go get him.
- 没问题的  - 小心点
- You be cool. - Take it easy.
恭喜你要当爸爸了 中尉
Good luck with that baby, Lieutenant.
- 大伙都知道了吗?  - 只有重要的人才知道
- Does everybody know?  - Only the important people.
对谁重要的人? 对你来说的?
The important people to who? You?
算是吧
I guess so.
- 我去跟兄弟们大概说下任务  - 嘿 等一下
- I'm gonna go brief the boys. - Hey, hold on one second.
老兄 我之前从来没写过这东西
Hey, brother, I've never written one of these before.
嘿 我是跟着你干的 长官
Hey, I'm tracking with you, Sir. I am.
但老实跟你说
But, to be honest with you,
我之前在考虑打给指挥部 希望能让回家
I was thinking of calling the command and trying to get you home.
但这会儿要做的事情这么多 我觉得我们真的很需要你
But now that work's picked up so much, I feel like we really need you here.
你记得我们上次在安巴尔的那次任务吗?
You remember our last cruise to Al Anbar?
- 记得啊  - 你在施行最后清剿的时候
- Yeah.  - When you had that final turnover op,
你说我可以去
and you said I didn't need to be there?
当时我就躺在床上
I was laying in bed and
我意识到我唯一要做的事情就是回家去
I realized the only thing I needed to do now was go home.
但如果你的任务有个闪失
But if something went south on your op,
我肯定会抱憾终身的
I would always regret not being there with you.
谢谢你一直以来的照顾  戴夫
I appreciate you taking care of me big-time, Dave,
我一直很上头在商量
but I'm working some things with the brass.
如果可以的话 等事态缓解了 我就放自己两周的假
If I can, and things slow down, I'm gonna get two weeks off.
不管怎么说 我都希望这事能早点解决 真的
Well, I hope it works out either way. I really do.
但万一出事的话 我就把这张纸
But, if it doesn't, I'm gonna take this piece of paper,
叠成一架纸飞机 然后飞出去了
and I'm gonna make it into a nice paper airplane.
滚吧你
Beat it.
非洲海岸
走吧 走吧!
We're good, we're good!
值更官 把潜艇下潜至160尺
Chief of the Watch, submerge the ship to one-six-zero feet.
下潜 下潜
Dive. Dive.
潜望镜收起 所有闸门密封
Scope down. All doors are green.
- 哦 好的 嘿 伙计们  - 长官
- Oh, good. Hey, guys.  - Sir.
- 多谢你们这么快就赶过来了  - 当然的
- Thank you for getting here so fast.  - Sure.
- 快坐下来吧  - 谢谢
- Grab a seat, please.  - Thank you.
"斗牛犬"直升机会在空中支援我们
You'll have Bulldog overhead.
我们需要你们潜入 获取情报
We need you to get in, grab the intel
然后回到我们这里 有问题吗?
and bounce it back to us. Do you have any questions?
长官 我有问题 我们明确了回合地点和时间
Sir, I have a question. We have the rally point and time.
那如果他们没按计划进行会面怎么办呢?
What if the meeting doesn't take place as scheduled?
我们得盯着目标多久呢?
How long do you want us to stay on target?
好问题 那你们就得在那呆上一段时间了
Now, this one counts, so I'd plan on being out there for a while.
- 明白  - 大伙都懂了吗?
- Check.  - Are we good?
- 懂了 长官  - 没问题 长官
- Think so, Sir.  - Yes, Sir.
瑞和阿杰穿戴完毕 准备出发
Ray and Ajay are rigged up and ready to check each other out.
闸门安全
Garage door clear.
索马里
- 你看得清楚吗?  - 行的
- You got a visual?  - Yeah.
有三辆卡车正在靠近
Got three trucks moving in.
一辆加油车 两辆吉普 坐着些非洲黑人
A fuel truck, two jeeps, some skinnies in the back.
其中一人装备着把.50口径机枪
One of them has a .50-cal.
你听到了吗?
You hear that?
- 听到了 应该是咱们的飞机来了  - 是啊 飞过来了
- Yeah, I think that's our plane.  - Yeah, we got some inbound.
这些家伙也该出现了 老天 等我拿出照相机
About time these guys showed up. Jesus. Let me get my camera.
嘿 瑞 飞机场尽头停着两架飞机
Hey, Ray, we got two birds down at the end of the field,
我们的东南边那架 机尾无编号
southeast our pos, no tail IDs.
- 你听到了吗?  - 明白 机尾无编号
- You got that?  - Check, no tail IDs.
瑞 没搞错的话 我们是在非洲吧?
Ray, last time I checked, we were in Africa, right?
是啊 怎么了?
Yeah. Why, what's up?
伙计的 那边好像有16个菲律宾人
Dude, there's, like, 16 Filipinos down there,
都在朝拜麦加呢
all praying to Mecca right now.
- 菲律宾人?  - 菲律宾人 绝对不是非洲人
- Filipinos?  - Filipinos. Definitely not skinnies.
我听到祈祷的声音 我还听到些俄语
I'm picking up the praying. I'm also picking up some Russian.
你们两个 过来
这些箱子拿的时候小心点 听到没有?
你要是有一个没拿稳 我们全部去见上帝
你去换架飞机
从两个不同的地方穿越边境
小心使得万年船
等到了岛上 你们再慢慢做准备
那边有朋友会接应你 带你走完剩下的"路"的
斗牛犬 斗牛犬 这是红.朗姆酒 检查电台通讯 完毕
Bulldog, Bulldog, Redrum, radio check, over.
- 通讯正常 完毕  - 收到 通讯正常
- Good check, copy.  - Roger, good check.
请注意 我们发现两家不明飞机
Be advised, we got two sterile aircraft
从以下坐标向东面飞去
departing to the east from following location:
10 P L S (美军三角定位法)
Ten, Papa, Lima, Sierra.
发现目标请回话 完毕
Please advise when tally target, over.
收到 两架飞机 位置 10 P...
Roger. Copy, two aircraft, location Ten, Papa...
嘿 船长 你肯定不会相信的?  (好人理查德号航空母舰 中美洲海岸)
Hey, Chief, you are not gonna believe this.
瑞和阿杰标记的两架飞机中的一架
One of the planes Ray and Ajay tagged
刚刚降落在墨西哥海岸的塞德罗斯岛上
just landed on Cedros Island off the coast of Mexico.
机上载着沙宝和数量不明的圣战分子
It has Shabal on it with an unknown number of jihadis.
你在开玩笑吧?
Are you kidding me?
没有 看起来我们要出手对付这目标了
No, looks like we're gonna get to hit that target.
军士长和特种部队战斗小组的快艇已经出击了
Well, Senior and the SWCC boats are punching out.
他们应该能给我们弄到些情报的 到时候看吧
They should pull a little more intel for us, so we'll see.
好的
All right.
我还不知道我们要呆多久 等一下 宝贝
I don't know how long we're staying. Hold on, baby.
- 注意安全  - 我会的
- Be safe.  - You know I will.
- 我要走了 宝贝  - 我爱你
- I gotta go, honey.  - I Iove you.
我也爱你
I love you.
琼 我不想你和那群男孩子玩在一起
你听见我说的了吗?
好的? 那好 我待会打给你
B队 A队 我们离目标200米
Bravo Alpha, we're 200 meters out.
B小队 右舷发现目标
Bravo, you have a Tango on your starboard side.
右舷发现目标
Tango on the starboard side.
战地指挥 我们发现目标
Whiskey Charlie, we have a visual on Tango.
B小队 12点钟方向有敌人
Bravo, you have a Viper at twelve o'clock.
趴下! 趴下!
Get down! Get down!
安全! 占领舰桥
Clear! Bridge secure.
长官 没问题了
Senior, you're clear.
下午好啊 你好吗?
你还好吧? 你会讲塞尔维亚-克罗地亚语吗?
会说俄语
你是俄罗斯人?
是的
我不会说俄罗斯语
- 用英语行吧? 那就这样好了  - 就用英语吧
- English OK? Let's do that.  - English is fine.
帮他松个绑吧?
Can you cut him loose, please?
给你松绑了 你不会做傻事吧?
If you get cut loose, you're not gonna do anything crazy, are you?
比如说 "疯子伊凡"?
A Crazy Ivan? So to speak.
那你是俄罗斯人 对吧?
So you're Russian, yeah?
- 没错  - 你没事吧?
- Yes, I am.  - You all right?
- 我没事 谢谢了  - 不用谢
- Yes, I'm good. Thank you.  - You're welcome.
不好意思 我都不知道你是哪位
I'm sorry. I don't know your name.
- 我叫奥托  - 奥托 你好
- I'm Otto.  - Otto.
- 好 那你是?  - 很高兴见到你
- Yes. And you are?  - Nice to meet you.
我叫克里斯托
Christo.
- 叫克里斯科?  - 是克里斯托
- Crisco? - Christo.
特拉伊卡维奇?
Troskawicz?
话说 我到底要纠缠你到何时
So how long am I gonna need to keep busting your balls
才能得到一块那样的标志啊?
about getting one of those patches?
哦 这个啊 我觉得不会再发了
Ah, yeah, I think it was, like, a one-time deal, man.
911之后 我叔叔给排里送了一批
After 9/11, my uncle sent a bunch out for the platoon,
这次行动完了之后 我把这个送给你好了
but, uh, after this go-round, I'll give it to you.
不用 不用 我才不会拿你们的家徽的
No, no, I'm not gonna take your family crest.
好极了 反正我也没真心打算给你
All right, good. I didn't want to give it to you anyway.
而且 我确定我看到你
Besides, man, I'm pretty sure I saw you
那天往大口袋里放了些东西的
putting something in your cargo pocket the other day.
- 怎么说?  - 我那天看到
- What's that?  - I know I've seen you carrying
你那边口袋有什么东西的
something in that pocket right there.
是什么东西?
What is it?
那是我祖父的旗帜(盖在棺材上的旗帜)
That's my grandfather's flag.
我爸爸把它传给了我
My pop gave it to me,
以后我要继续传给我的儿子
and now I'm gonna give it to my boy someday.
好的 这传统我喜欢
All right. I like that.
你的船不错的样子啊
You're sitting on a wonderful boat.
- 这船简直是好极了  - 谢谢
- It's fabulous.  - Thank you. Yes.
- 我叫它 星舰船  - 星舰船
- I believe it's called "Starship".  - "Starship."
我喜欢你说星舰船的样子
I Iove the way you say Starship.
像极了俄罗斯人 那个.... 星际迷航里的那个人
It's Iike Russian. That guy, uh... "Star Trek".
叫什么来着 斯科蒂? 哦 不对 叫斯科特
What's his name, Scotty? Oh, no, he was, sorry, Scott.
- 我怎么会知道  - 好吧 你从来没看过星际迷航?
- I wouldn't know.  - Yes. You've never seen Star Trek?
- 没看过  - 哦 这没道理啊
- No.  - Oh, that's insane.
伙计 你的问题就在这里
So here's the problem, pal.
你值很多钱
You're worth a lot of money.
- 或者你之前值很多钱  - 我相信现在我也值很多钱
- Or you were worth a lot of money.  - I believe I still am.
- 是吗?  - 是的
- You do?  - Yes.
好吧 就让我来告诉你 这世道的规矩是怎么样的吧 克里斯科
All right. Let me tell you how the world works there, Crisco.
- 是叫克里斯托  - 再说一遍?
- It's Christo. - Sorry?
- 是克里斯托  - 哦 不好意思
- Christo.  - Oh, of course. Sorry.
没事
It's OK.
我来告诉你这世道是怎么样的吧
Let me tell you how the world really works.
- 说吧  - 这船已经不是你的了
- Please.  - This is no longer your boat.
从我走进来那刻起 你就不是之前那个你了
Since I walked through that door, you're not the same guy you used to be.
就是这样 我也没办法阻止这一切
You're just not. There's nothing I can do to stop that,
除非你让我帮你 不让我也没法帮你
nothing I can do to help you right now, unless you let me help you.
你和我之间 我们需要同心协力 伙计
We need to do this together, pal. You and me.
那你和那些圣战分子搞在一起感觉怎么样啊?
So how is it that you're working with these jihadi folks, then?
你是犹太人 没错吧?
You're Jewish, right?
沙宝是谁?
Shabal is what?
- 你有从小穿裤裆的伙伴吗?  - 你说什么?
- You got a friend, like, you grew up with?  - Sorry?
你有那种从小一起长大的伙伴吗?
Have you ever had a friend that you grew up with?
- 有啊  - 有共同爱好的 踢足球啊
- Yes.  - Had, like, played interests, played soccer,
或者... 你们是玩什么? 可能是棒球 对吧?
or... What would you play? Baseball, probably, right?
- 算是吧 好吧  - 好吧
- Probably. Yeah. - Yeah.
之后你们分道扬镳
And then you went on your separate ways,
然后几年之前 你又再聚首
and then some years later, you meet up.
但你完全认不出那个人了
And you totally didn't recognize the person.
沙宝就是这么个情况
And that's what happened with Shabal.
我们志向相同
We share a common interest.
他就着他的信仰 想出了这个惊人的主意
So he came up with this incredible idea because of his beliefs.
我虽然和他有不同的信仰 但他可是个聪明人
I don't necessarily share his beliefs, but he's a smart guy.
就好像是...
You know, it's almost like...
you know, it's almost Iike...
这个就好像是我
like this is me.
- 而那个就是沙宝  - 是吗?
- And that's Shabal.  - Is it?
- 美国就夹在中间  - 是吗?
- And America is in-between.  - Is it?
没错
Yeah.
这比喻不错吧?
Cool concept, no?
- 夹在中间?  - 是的
- Right here?  - Yes.
你以为这是场游戏吗?
You think this is some kind of game?
问你呢? 你觉得这样很有意思吗?
Do you? Do you find this amusing?
- 我没觉得...  - 你知道你在做什么吗?
- I'm not finding...  - Do you realize what you're doing here?
黑胡子小队 这里是黑胡子总部
Blackbeard Actual, Blackbeard Main.
通过全体队员 B目标已清除
Post nation counterpart. Secured target Bravo.
三号船报告 你们可安全前往A目标
Report to Tri-Hull. You're clear to move on target Alpha.
收到 总部 占领目标
Roger, Main. Clear to target.
我需要交代的人 就只有我家里人
The only people I answer to is my family.
我妻子和我孩子
To my wife and to my child.
没其他人的事
And nobody else.
- 赶时间啊?  - 废话太多了
- Running late somewhere? - Shit filter's full.
- 是吗?  - 没错
- Really?  - Yeah.
伙计 那现在情况是这样的
So here's the problem, pal.
你在乎你家里人 对吧?
You do love your family, don't you?
- 是的  - 那在乎你女儿不?
- Yes, I do.  - And what about your daughter?
我女儿怎么了?
What about my daughter?
你还想再见到她吗?
Are you looking forward to seeing her again?
就没有不想过
Every minute of my life.
我给你看这个
I wanted you to see that
是让你仔细考虑一下
so that you'd think about some things very seriously,
因为你马上就要被关起来
because you're gonna be sitting in a box somewhere.
得到合适的人性的对待
You'll be treated properly and humanely.
你女儿将会长大成人 嫁人生子
That girl is gonna grow up, and she's gonna get married,
你妻子也会另觅新欢
and your wife is gonna find someone else,
而你将会一无所有
and you're gonna miss everything.
如果因为我的所作所为威胁到我的家人
If I had done something that would endanger my family,
我肯定和你现在的感觉一样
I would feel just like you do right now.
你保证不害我家人?
You promise not to touch my family?
我永远不会害你的家人
I would never touch your family.
永远不会
I would not.
你听说过...
Are you familiar with...
陶瓷球背心吗?
ceramic ball bearings?
没听过
No.
那想象一下 16件装满
Just imagine 16 suicide vests
陶瓷弹珠的自杀背心
filled with those ceramic ball bearings,
逃过你们国家金属探测器和各处卡点的检查
slipping by every metal detector and every checkpoint in your country.
你一定觉得你们国家的经济将要完蛋了吧?
You think your economy is fucked now?
想想媒体会怎么大肆宣传这事吧 懂吗?
Just think what the media is gonna do with this. Hm?
到时候911事件候 看起来就像是在公园溜弯一样
It's gonna make 9/11 look like a fucking walk in the park.
在中央花园溜个弯而已 简直弱爆了
The grand Central Park.
你是在说...
So you're telling me...
有16个穿自杀背心的圣战分子
there's 16 jihadis wearing suicide vests.
他们准备大摇大摆地入境
They're gonna walk right across the border.
那他们要去哪里?
So where are they going?
圣地亚哥 圣弗朗西斯科 休斯顿...
San Diego, San Francisco, Houston...
城市随你选 他们随叫随到
You pick a city, they'll be there.
- 他们现在就开始行动了吗?  - 我们谈话的时候 就开始了
- And this is happening now? - It's happening as we speak.
不好意思 再说一遍?
Sorry, what?
我们谈话的时候 就开始了
It's happening as we speak.
你怎么样才能阻止这一切?
How can you stop this?
我也没办法
I can't.
墨西哥 塞德罗斯岛
黑胡子头儿 已经包围目标
Blackbeard Lead, containment element is set.
收到
Roger.
卡洛斯 门口有人!
救命啊! 救命啊!
枪! 有枪!
Gun! Gun! Gun!
安全!
Clear!
- 撤  - 我们出来了!
- Go.  - Coming out!
鼠帮 我是黑胡子 我们在教堂南面 市中心 开始进攻
Rat Pack, this is Blackbeard. We're in contact, midtown, south of the church.
发现敌人!
Contact!
有敌人!
换弹夹!
Changing!
黑胡子头儿 你在什么位置?
Blackbeard Lead, what's your pos?
掩护射击 你们可以前进
Overwatch. You're clear to engage.
全力开火
Go in hot.
扔雷啦!
Frag out!
维明 有两个人带喷射枪开着小卡车往南走了
Weimy, I've got two squirters heading south in a pickup truck.
看见他们了
I see 'em.
干掉小卡车上那两个人
Hit those two guys in the truck.
火箭炮!
Rocket!
扔雷了!
Frag out!
长官? 长官?
Sir? Sir?
中尉? 你还好吧?
LT? You all right?
妈的
Damn.
你检查那个盒子了 是吗?
You check that box, huh?
是
Yeah.
幸好是个哑弹 要不然我就挂啦
Good thing that was a dud. I might've gotten hurt.
- 是啊  - 喔
- Yeah.  - Whoa.
天啊
Jesus.
这绝不是伊拉克小草屋里制作出来的劣质爆破马甲
This is not some bush-league vest from an Iraqi hut.
这是一些高速易爆物
This is some high-speed shit.
那我还是先把这玩意放远一点吧?
Maybe we should put this somewhere else, huh?
嘿 索尼 把这个放别处 好吗?
Hey, Sonny, find somewhere to put this, would you?
目标安全 做好警戒工作
Target secure. Set security.
一个在北边守着 三个在南边守着
One's to the north, three south.
这就是你们的目标
嗯...
我为你们感到骄傲
我们现在是一家人
嘿 长官 目标安排妥当了
Hey, Chief, target's buttoned up.
- 一切都安全  - 谢了 哥们儿
- Everything's secure.  - Thanks, man.
行动人员 任务还未完成 原地待命
Actual, mission not complete. Stand by for follow-on.
你们只击毙了一半的圣战主义恐怖分子
You only got half that jihadist cell.
- 目标安全了 长官  - 战斗还没结束
- The target's secure, sir.  - This fight isn't over yet.
现在 听着 另一半恐怖分子将会在早上7点的时候
Now, Listen, the other half of that cell is gonna be crossing the border
利用墨西卡利的隧道网络 穿过边境
using a tunnel network from Mexicali at 0700.
我们现在正在跟国家协调 但是现在飞机会带你们
We're coordinating with State, but for now the birds will drop you off
到城市周边 在那儿你们的指挥官是佩德罗斯长官
outside the city where your POC is a Commander Pedros.
在路上的时候我会告诉你们细节
I'll give you more details en route.
- 行动人员 收到了吗?  - 报告总部 收到
- Actual, how do you copy?  - Roger, Main.
好了 直升机来接我们了
OK, we've got a helo landing on the deck,
我们要去跟墨西哥特种部队指挥官和他的小队汇合
we're gonna meet a Mexican SOF commander and his team.
他们将帮助我们找到目标 一起发起攻击
They're gonna help infil us to the target and join us on the assault.
- 你说这话什么意思?  - 还有些余孽没清除 长官
- What the hell are you talking about?  - We haven't got all of 'em yet, Chief.
- 那剩下的在哪儿?  - 在墨西卡利的边境
- And where's the rest of 'em?  - They're in Mexicali on the border.
好 那剩下的战友
All right. And the rest of the boys,
他们怎么回到船上?
how are they getting back to the ship?
本.欧姆.理查德继续留在驻地
Bon Homme Richard stayed on station.
他们会派名海军陆战队员来盘问目标
They're gonna send in a Marine element to help exploit the target.
完成后 剩下的战友跟他们一起撤退
When they're done, the boys will pull off with them.
好 那我和一队先去
OK. I'm thinking Squad One and myself roll out.
很好 二队先留在这儿准备善后
Perfect. Squad Two stays here, buttons it up,
- 再跟海军一起撤离  - 好的
- pulls out with the Marines.  - OK.
我们往北走
We're moving north of here through town,
日出之前穿过市中心
and crossing at sunrise.
另一组第二天会穿过华瑞兹市(墨西哥城市)
The other group will get into Texas the following day,
到达德克萨斯州
through Juarez.
明白了吗?
Comprendes?
嘿 长官! 谁他妈的让咱们这么匆忙的赶去墨西卡利?
Hey, sir! Who the hell cleared us hot to go to Mexicali anyway?
这人可大有来头啊
This one's going all the way up the flagpole.
国务院下的命令
State Department's on it.
美国与墨西哥边境墙
嘿 长官 频道二
Hey, sir. Channel two.
嘿 以这个速度
Hey, this tempo keeps up like this,
杰基就得自己在家生孩子了
Jackie's gonna be squeezing that kid out on her own.
但是 如果我们速度搞定这个任务 你就可以骑个小毛驴赶回家了
However, we hit this target quick enough, you jump on a burro and ride that shit home.
嘿 我可不需要小毛驴
Hey, I ain't gonna need no burro.
你两个礼拜的假请下来了吗?
Did you get your two weeks?
我打那么久卫星电话
All that time I was spending on the sat phone,
可不是在说服他们让我回家
it wasn't to convince them to let me go home,
而是想说服他们让你领导这次行动
it was to convince them to leave your ass in charge.
美国与墨西哥边境 北纬32度 西经117度
- 长官  - 中尉
- Sir.  - Lieutenant.
看来政府真是想让咱们合作 是不?
Seems our governments have been very busy to make this possible, huh?
据我所知 是上头下来的命令
All the way to the top, from what I hear.
有些事你必须得明白
There is something that you have to understand.
我的上级 他们非常害怕墨西哥出个摩加迪沙
My superiors, they're very fearful of a Mexican Mogadishu.
他们可不想这里再次上演 黑鹰坠落啊
No Black Hawk Down is what they're saying,
所以我们得低调行动
so we do need to stay under the radar.
- 我完全明白 长官  - 那就好
- I understand completely, sir.  - Good.
您的小组能来我们非常感激 但是我们时间紧迫
Your team's presence here is greatly appreciated, but we are out of time.
- 我们得立刻行动  - 告诉我去哪儿 我们立刻就走
- We need to move.  - Tell me where, we go.
帮我分析一下
Help piece this together for me.
- 好的  - 我们收到的情报是
- OK.  - Our intel says
他们用的是一家牛奶工厂下面的隧道网络
they're using a tunnel network that is under a milk factory.
你能想到什么吗?
This mean anything to you?
我知道确切位置 离这儿不远
I know exactly where that is. It's not far from here.
那我们就去那儿
Then that's where we're going.
在墨西卡利 你们去的这个地方
Of all of the places in Mexicali
大概是最危险的地方
that you could have picked, this is probably the worst.
墨西哥毒枭把那个地区守的严严实实
The cartels control that area from all angles.
我们火力不够
They have us heavily outgunned.
能接近你的目标就已经非常难了
Simply reaching your target is gonna be very difficult.
长官 现在有八个外籍人士想要进入我们国家
Sir, we have eight foreign nationals heading to our country.
不用说 他们不怀好意
Needless to say, they are no big fan of ours.
如果他们在那个工厂 我们就去那儿
If they are at that factory, that's where we're going.
中士 你要去哪儿我都带你去
Lieutenant, I'll take you anywhere you need to go,
但是你和你的人要做好准备 这将是一场你想象不到的恶战
but prepare your men for a bigger fight than what you had imagined.
你不仅是跟八个人战斗 你还要跟保护他们的墨西哥毒枭战斗
You're not fighting eight men. You're also fighting the cartel that's protecting them.
如果你的目标进入这些隧道
If your targets make it into those tunnels,
他们会像鬼一样消失
they'll disappear like ghosts.
你们从这儿进入隧道
You enter the tunnels right here.
然后走七英里到这个分叉口
You will walk seven miles to this fork.
我的人会告诉你们走哪条隧道
My men will tell you what tunnel to take.
一旦你到这个点 我的任务就算完成了
Once you get to this point, my job is done.
你们就自求多福了
You're on your own.
- 中士 我们要行动了!  - 收到
- Lieutenant, we're going now!  - Roger that.
长官 不要停 我们直逼目标
Chief, we're not stopping. We're rolling up on target, hard.
收到 长官 我们还有大概三十秒就到了
Roger that, sir. We're about 30 seconds out.
南面进口处有人影窜动
One mike out from the south entrance.
杰夫! 屋顶有人!
Jefe! On the roof!
我们得撤了 马上
We gotta go. Now.
我们走
你留在这儿
长官! 留两个人在这儿!
Sir! Leave two men here!
准备好 他们来了
维明!
Weimy!
你把他们搞定他们!
I need you to lock this shit down!
扔雷了!
Frag out!
掩护我
On me.
你们去大门那边!
You guys got the gate!
卡尔! 你去前门!
Call! You're going to the front door!
上!
Go!
卡尔!
Call!
需要你的时候到了
怎么了?
你会在天堂见到你丈夫的
换弹夹!
Changing!
有炸弹!
Bomb!
为什么停下来?
是你 长官
Damn it, sir.
刚才的事你怎么给我家人解释?
How you gonna explain that one to my family?
你回去我就不用解释了 是吧?
Get back there so I don't have to, huh?
安全!
Clear!
手榴弹!
Grenade!
中士!
LT!
长官 他交给我吧
Chief, I got him.
继续前进 我掩护你
Keep going. I'll cover you.
进隧道
长官
Chief.
长官!
Chief!
二分队 我是一分队
Assault Two, this is Assault One.
报告 隧道已经安全 所有威胁都已经解除
Be advised, tunnel is secure and all threats are neutralized.
中士和长官倒下了
LT and Chief are down.
再说一遍 中士和长官倒下了
I say again, LT and Chief are down.
你父亲是个好人
Your father was a good man.
成长中没有他的陪伴一定很艰难
Growing up without him is gonna be hard.
肯定会痛苦
It's gonna hurt.
你会感到孤独 就像到了海里 看不到岸
You'll feel alone, out to sea, with no shore in sight.
你会问自己 "为什么我没父亲? 为什么我父亲死了?"
You'll wonder, "Why me? Why him?"
记住 你身体流着勇士的血
Remember, you have warrior's blood in your veins.
与你父亲一样 你身上遗传了他特有的遗传密码
The code that made your father who he was is the same code
使你成为了像他一样令人爱戴尊敬的人
that'll make you a man he would admire, respect.
把你的痛苦放进一个盒子 锁上
Put your pain in a box. Lock it down.
就像你父亲喜欢的那些油画里的人一样
Like those people in the paintings your father liked,
我们的人生中有束缚 有失去 有胜利
we are men made up of boxes, chambers of loss and triumph,
有伤痛 有希望 有爱
of hurt and hope and love.
- 一个人如果能驾驭自己的感情...  - 准备!
- No one is stronger or more dangerous...  - Ready!
- ...那没有人比他更强大或者危险  - 瞄准!
- ...than a man who can harness his emotions.  - Aim!
他的过去
His past.
瞄准!
Aim!
利用它当成燃料 当成弹药
Use it as fuel, as ammunition,
当成墨水 写下你生活中最浓墨重彩的篇章
as ink to write the most important letter of your life.
我代表美国总统
On behalf of the President of the United States
一个充满感激的国家 为您献上这面旗
and a grateful nation, I present you this flag
以表彰您丈夫的英雄事迹
in recognition of your husband's heroic achievements.
致以我最深切的悼念
You have my deepest condolences.
还有一面旗献给您
One more flag to present.
我想您很熟悉这面旗
This one I think you know.
每次任务 洛克都带着它
On every deployment, Rorke carried this with him.
再一次致以我最深切的悼念
Again, my deepest condolences.
恩格中士!
Lieutenant Engel!
恩格中士请安息!
Hoo-yah, Lieutenant Engel!
你父亲临死之前 让我把特库姆塞的这首诗给你
Before he died, your father asked me to give you this poem by Tecumseh.
我告诉他我会把这张纸叠成纸飞机
I told him I'd fold it into a paper airplane.
某种程度上来说 我想我正是这么做的
And, in a way, I guess that's what I'm doing,
把这纸飞机飞向你
sailing it from him to you.
好好生活 让死亡的恐惧
Live your life that the fear of death
永远不会侵蚀你的心
can never enter your heart
不要诋毁他人的信仰
Trouble no one about his religion
尊重他人 尊重他人的观点
Respect others and their views
同时要求他人尊重你
And demand they respect yours
热爱你的生活 完善你的生活
Love your life, perfect your life
美化你生命中的一切
Beautify all things in your life
努力延长你的生命 为他人服务
Seek to make your life long and of service to your people
当你要离开这个世界的时候
When your time comes to die
不要让死亡的恐惧充斥着你的内心
Be not like those whose hearts are filled with fear of death
当死亡来临的时候 不要哭泣着祈祷
So that when their time comes they weep and pray
能够有少许时间重活一次
For a little more time to live their lives over again in a different way
高唱死亡之歌
Sing your death song
像一个英雄回家一样离开
And die like a hero going home
此电影献给911事件后为国家安全做出牺牲的海军特种作战勇士
也献给即将赶赴战场的勇士
勇者行动
有勇士就有希望
# 映入眼帘的只有硝烟战场 #
# All I saw was smoke and fire #
# 我毫无感觉 #
# I didn't feel a thing #
# 但突然我被捧上云端 #
# But suddenly I was rising higher #
# 感觉我犯了一个 #
# And I felt like I just made #
# 人生中最大的错误 #
# the biggest mistake #
# 当我想起我未出生的孩子 #
# When I thought about my unborn child #
# 当我想起我的妻子 #
# And when I thought about my wife #
# 答案变得明朗 #
# And the answer rang out clear #
# 在我脑海中呈现 #
# From somewhere up above #
# 对于一个男人 没有什么礼物 #
# No greater gift has man #
# 可以比得上为爱献出一切 #
# Than to lay down his life for love #
# 我想 #
# And I wonder #
# 我愿意献出生命吗? #
# Would I give my life? #
# 我会做出如此牺牲吗? #
# Could I make that sacrifice? #
# 如果真要抉择 我会冲向枪口吗?
# If it came down to it Could I take the bullet? #
# 我会 是的 我会 #
# I would Yes, I would #
# 为你献出生命 #
# For you #
# 嗯-嗯 #
# Mm-hm #
# 或许你不明白 #
# Maybe you don't understand #
# 我自己也不明白 #
# I don't understand it all myself #
# 但是兄弟们就在我身边 #
# But there's a brother on my left and another on my right #
# 他的衣兜里也和我一样 #
# And in his pocket just like mine #
# 放着一张照片 #
# He's got a photograph #
# 家人等待他回家 #
# And they're waiting for him back home #
# 这一直萦绕在我脑海 #
# And it's weighing on my mind #
# 我不是要做一个英雄 #
# I'm not trying to be a hero #
# 我也不想死 #
# I don't wanna die #
# 但在此时此刻 #
# But right now in this moment #
# 你不能犹豫 #
# You don't think twice #
# 我不知道我会不会献出我的生命 #
# I wonder Would I give my life #
# 我会做出那样的牺牲吗? #
# Could I make that sacrifice? #
# 如果真要抉择 我会冲向枪口吗? #
# If it came down to it Could I take the bullet? #
# 我会 是的 我会 #
# I would Yes, I would #
# 不要想对 #
# You don't think about right #
# 还是错 #
# You don't think about wrong #
# 你只能履行职责 #
# You just do what you gotta do #
# 捍卫自己的尊严 #
# To defend your own #
# 我也会这样做 #
# And I'd do the same #
# 为了你 是的 我愿意 #
# For you Yes, I would #
# 是的 我愿意 #
# Yes, I would #
# 我愿意献出生命 #
# I would give my life #
# 我愿意做出牺牲 #
# I would make that sacrifice #
# 因为当你真要抉择 #
# 'Cause if it came down to it #
# 我愿冲向枪口吗? 我愿意 #
# Could I take a bullet? I would #
# 是的 我愿意
# Yes, I would #
# 我会为你付出一切 #
# I'd do it for you #
# 是的 #
# Yeah #
# 我愿为你献出一切 #
# I'd do it for you #
# 哦 #
# Oh #
# 冲向枪口 #
# Take the bullet #
# 是的 #
# Yeah #
# 是的 我愿意 #
# Yes, I would #
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
协调：心仪Sally
翻译：爱上某某的FAFA 死神夜月 RK翔 Tracy
校对：影子 心仪Sally